PERSONAL

- Name
 Kiran Kumar C
- ★ Address Rajarajeshwari layout, Challegatta 560060 Bangalore
- Phone number 8073508401
- Email kiranc2210@gmail.com
- EinkedIn linkedin.com/in/kiran-kumar-ca82344161

KIRAN KUMAR C

Over 4.9 years of experience in that 2.9+ yeas in Software Manual and Automation Testing for Web-based and Mobile application. Hardworking Automation Tester versed in coordinating projects and maintaining documentation. Creates new test cases and test scripts. Expert in full automation frameworks and tools. and To give effective as well as efficient efforts towards the attainment of organizational goals with exploring the wide scope of knowledge and intelligence. To work in an environment that provides a challenging and rewarding career ensuring high-level job satisfaction. In the process apart from benefiting my employer, I also expect to learn for my overall development. and Self-motivated, energetic and highly ethical in all work related assignments thus able to immediately contribute to corporate goals and object.



WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2019 - Present

Automation Test Engineer

Libre Wireless Technologies India pvt ltd, Bangalore

Roles and Responsibilities

- Developed in Automation Framework implementing Page Object Model, using the Java, Selenium Web Driver, and Cucumber.
- Performed BDD using the Cucumber Features, Scenarios, and Step Definitions in Gherkin Format.
- Experience on Core Java, OOPS concepts.
- implemented Maven for build Management, and Jerkins for Continuous Integration of the build.
- Assessed and analyzed user stories and participated in Sprint Planning,
 Review Sessions & Scrum Meeting and developed Test Scenarios, Test
 cases, Test Data, Test procedures, Test reports.
- Performed **User Acceptance Testing** exclusively in an **agile** environment.
- Implemented **Selenium Web driver** to run automated test cases in **multiple browsers** and **cross Platforms.**
- Implemented Scripts for Mobile applications for IOS and Android using Appium on Windows and MAC.
- Performed UI, Functional, Regression testing by automation using the Selenium Web Driver, Features, Maven, and integrated Scripts to CI/CD tool Jenkins for nightly consignment run of the scripts.
- Designed the test scripts and analyzed the results in various levels of the
 applications including Integration, Regression, Functional, and
 acceptance testing using the Selenium web driverand Applium for
 mobile applications.
- Participated in Stand-up meetings, walkthrough meetings, weekly automation meetings with all other QA, weekly assessment meetings with scrum master and developers
- Strong Problem-solving skills and ability to troubleshoot applications & environmental issues.
- Good **Analytical skills** & Business thinking and ability to learn faster.

Mar 2017 - Apr 2019

Customer Support Executive

Hinduja Global Solutions, Bangalore

Roles and Responsibilities

- Build rapport with customers by engaging with them in an inviting, friendly, and professional manner, to deliver exceptional experiences nurture lasting relationships.
- Respond quickly, professionally, and accurately to all customer inquiries regarding quotes, orders, status requests, complaints, product returns, and warranties.



EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Jun 2012 - Jul 2016

BE in Computer Science and Engineering

Govt. Engineering College, Ramanagara

Aug 2007 - Jul 2010

Diploma in Computer Science and Engineering

PVP Polytechnic, Bangalore



SKILLS

Testing Tools:Selenium Web **** Driver, Eclipse, Appium Frameworks: TestNG, Page $\star\star\star\star\star$ Object Model, Data-Driven Defect Tracking Tools: Bugzilla. 🖈 🖈 🖈 🖈 **Test Build and Integration** **** tools: Jenkins, Maven. **Programming Languages: Core** Java. Scripting Languages: python. $\star\star\star\star\star$ Markup Languages: HTML, XML, Xpath, CSS. Operating System: Windows, Ubuntu $\star\star\star\star\star$



STRENGTHS

- 1) Should Be detail oriented
- 2) Should be patient and resilience
- 3) Should be aggressive, adaptability
- 4) Should be Test to break attitude
- 5) Should have good writing skills
- 6) Good team player